This document is strictly private, confidential, and personal to its recipients and should not be copied, distributed, or reproduced in whole or in part, nor passed to any third party.

Boya Chiou

106 Da'an District, Taipei City, Taiwan email : boya.chiou@gmail.com mobile : +886-90-5533-115

Boya is currently a Portfolio Manager, managing multi-asset/REITs portfolios at Cathay SITE, Taiwan's largest asset management company with over \$30 Billion AUM. Boya has developed expertise in investment analysis, asset allocation, and portfolio management with about 7 years of working experience in the financial industry. Boya also worked in close collaboration with other Tier 1 global Private Equity partners for alternative product design and delivery for private banking, high-net-worth individuals, professional investors, and institutional clients.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2019 —

Portfolio Manager, Cathay SITE, Cathay Financial Holdings, Taipei Investment Analysis/Portfolio Management

- Designed, constructed, implemented, and maintained alternative investment, REITs fund of funds. Expected annualized return 6-12%, sharp ratio > 1.5-2.5. Passed down knowledge and procedures to following fund
- Optimized, implemented, and maintained fixed income/bond ETF fund model and portfolio
- Public non-listed REITs, covering the full spectrum of real estate sector; residential, multi family, hotel hospitality, retail, industrial and healthcare centers, etc
- Roadshow, product promotion for private banking, high-net-worth individuals, professional investors and institutional clients, etc
- Product structure
- Department budgeting and planning

Dec 2018 — May 2019

Assistant Manager, Taishin Financial Holdings, Taipei

Investment Analysis

- Conducted fundamental investment analysis of Nikkei 225, TOPIX, power, utilities, infrastructure, renewable energy
- Uncovered an undervalued utility stock, which rebounded by over 391% within 1 month
- Monitored sector news promptly and concisely conveyed information to stakeholders; delivered daily, monthly, and quarterly commentary
- Non-cyclical stocks

Oct 2017 — Oct 2018

Senior Specialist, Cathay Life Insurance, Cathay Financial Holdings, Taipei Investment Analysis

Cathay Life is the largest life insurance company and buy-side investor in Taiwan, with an AUM: USD\$ 267B As of 2020

- Created and maintained financial models, valuation frameworks, and investment theses
- Presented and defended investment recommendations to portfolio managers and made profitable calls for infrastructure stocks and Nikkei 225 Index
- Conducted Nikkei 225, TOPIX high dividend growth portfolio construction strategy, based on an empirical study
- Created a portfolio attribution analysis module using Python and automated abnormal stock volatility calculations using VBA
- Infrastructure, non-cyclical stocks

Jan 2017 — Oct 2017

Consultant, Kamakura Corporation, Asia-Pacific

Quantitative Analysis

- Provided pre-sales support and advised institutional clients on ALM (Asset Liability Management) analysis framework, including hedge fund, asset management, financial conglomerate banking clients in the Asia Pacific
- Developed statistical models and data analysis pipelines using Python and SQL database

Mar 2014 — Nov 2015

Analyst, Crédit Agricole Corporate and Investment Bank, Tokyo

- Conducted financial modeling of capital market activities and liquidity index report to support management's capital budgeting decisions and signified liquidity risk
- Supported the Treasury Unit for overnight rates calculation and liquidity control
- Programming assignments for internal trading tools development using Python and SQL database

Feb 2010 — May 2010

Intern, U.S. Chamber of Commerce, Washington D.C.

- Supported policy campaigns, high-level events, and meetings, e.g. luncheon with Prime Minister of Singapore, President of Vietnam, Vice President of Spain, African Union Trade & Investment Talk, and American diplomats with representatives from client companies
- Screened investment and business headline in Pakistan and updated and modified investment guidelines
- Promoted online campaigns by giving timely updates for business events of the US-Pakistan Business Council

LANGUAGE / TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Licenses & Certifications: Senior Securities Specialist (證券商高級業務員 Registered in April 2019), Securities Investment Trust and Consulting Professionals (投信投顧業務員 Registered in May 2019), expecting AICPA exams in 2021 (eligible for USCPA New York State)
- **Programming**: Python, SQL, data analysis, backtesting
- Languages: Mandarin Chinese (native), English (fluent; TOEIC 965), Japanese (intermediate; JLPT N1 Mock 117/180)

EDUCATION

2011 – 2013

Master of Public Policy

University of Tokyo, Tokyo, Japan; Concentration: Economics

2006 - 2010

Bachelor of Business Administration, GPA 3.8/4.0

National Taiwan University of Science and Technology, Taipei, Taiwan;

Concentration: Finance & Accounting, eligible for the CPA/AICPA New York exams

2008 - 2009

Economics, 1-year Exchange Program, Full Scholarship Awarded

Univerzita Pardubice, Pardubice, Czech Republic